Guide to the Irving McNeil Ives papers, 1862-1958
Ives, Irving McNeil papers, 1862-1958
- SERIES I. CORRESPONDENCE and LEGISLATION
  - [U. S. Senate] N. L. R. B. - Rules and Regulations - 191934-1947 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    labor (NLRB Reports); National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
  - [U. S. Senate] NLRB - Decisions - 191948 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    labor (NLRB decisions)
  - [U. S. Senate] NLRB Monthly Summaries - 1948-1949 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    labor (NLRB - reports)
  - [U. S. Senate] Reports - Labor and Public Welfare (LPW) - 1953 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    82nd Congress; labor management relations; Hubert H. Humphrey
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW Subcommitte on Health - 82nd Congress - 1951-1952 (Box 198, Folder 17)
    health; Lister Hill, Herbert H. Lehman
  - [U. S. Senate] Health Subcommittee Bills - 82nd" - 1951 (Box 198, Folder 18)
    health (legislation)
  - [U. S. Senate] Javits Health Bill - 1951 (Box 198, Folder 19)
    health services (legislation); Jacob K. Javits
  - [U. S. Senate] Labor Mgt. Subcommittee 82nd Congress - 1st Session 1951 - 1951 (Box 198, Folder 20)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on LPW - Labor Mgmt. Subcommittee); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Hubert H. Humphrey
  - [U. S. Senate] Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations - LPW - 82nd, 2nd, 1952 - 1952 (Box 198, Folder 21)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on LPW - Labor Management Subcommittee); National Consumers League; Hubert H. Humphrey, Edward Corsi
  - I.M.I. - Subcommittee on Labor and Labor-Management Relations - Reed Prince Manufacturing Co. - 1951-1952 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on Labor and Public Welfare - Labor Management Subcommittee)
  - LPW - General Information - 1953-1954 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    labor (legislation); Hubert H. Humphrey, H. Alexander Smith, Herbert H. Lehman
  - LPW - General Information - II - 1953-1954 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    labor (legislation), labor management relations
  - I.M.I. - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    U. S. Senate (LPW Comm.)
  - Bills - LPW Committee - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    labor (legislation), public welfare (legislation); 83rd Congress
  - Bills - LPW Committee - 2 - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Bills - LPW Committee - 3 - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Bills - LPW Committee - 4 - 1953-1954 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    labor (legislation), public welfare (legislation)
  - Bills - LPW Committee - 5 - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    labor (legislation), Public welfare (legislation); 83rd
  - Subcommittee on LPW (pending Bills) - 1953-1954 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on Labor and Public Welfare)
  - Senate Resolutions - LPW Committee - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    consumer interests (legislation), veterans affairs
  - Special Subcommittee on Rules (Labor Committee) - 1954 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    U. S. Senate (Labor Comm. - rules)
  - Subcommittee on Civil Rights - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    civil rights (legislation)
  - Sub-Committee on Labor - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    labor management relations (legislation), Taft-Hartley Act; H. Alexander Smith
  - U. S. House of Representatives - Legislative Calendar - 83rd Congress Comm. on Education and Labor - 1954 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    U. S. House of Representatives (legislative calendar)
  - Railroad retirement - 83rd Congress - 1953-1954 (Box 199, Folder 16-17)
    railroad retirement (legislation)
  - S.2930 Smith (I.M.I. co-sponsor) Amend RR Retirement Act, RR Retirement Tax Act, RR unemployment Insurance Act. "Labor - 83rd Congress - 1953-1954 (Box 199, Folder 18)
  - HR 356, S.2178 - Amending R. R. Retirement Act of 1937, so as to eliminate reductions of annuities and pensions in certain cases. 83rd Congress - 1954 (Box 199, Folder 19)
  - Albert C. Beeson - Hearings before Senate Labor Committee - 1954 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    U. S. Senate (presidential appointment); AFL; James E. Murray, Lister Hill
  - Comm. on Labor and Public Welfare (Nominations) - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous hearings - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 22)
    U. S. Senate (presidential appointment); hearings on Mr. Eisenhower's original cabinet - see list in folder
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Health Subcommittee - 83rd Congress - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 23)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] S.1970 (see S.1153 - 83rd) I.M.I. - Flanders National Health Act - 1949-1953 (Box 199, Folder 24)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] S.1153 - I.M.I.-Flanders - Facilitate broader distribution of health services, etc. Folder 2 - 1953 (Box 199, Folder 25)
    health (legislation); Ralph E. Flanders, Jacob K. Javits)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] S.1153 - 1953-1954 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] S.1153 Labor - I.M.I.-Flanders - facilitate broader distribution of health services, etc. - 1953-1954 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on LPW, Subcommittee on Health)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Joint Comm. on Mental Illness and Health. 1st Annual Report. 1956 - 1956-1957 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    mental health
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Administrations Legislative Program - Department of Health, Education and Welfare - 1954 (Box 200, Folder 4-5)
    health (legislation); 83rd Congress 2nd session
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] HR 5740 Amendment - Pure Food and Drug Act - Legislation - Correspondence - 1953 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    public welfare (Pure Food and Drug Act), public welfare (legislation); Hubert H. Humphrey
  - Legislative Calendar: U. S. Senate Committee on LPW - 84th Congress - 1956 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    U. S. Senate (legislative calendar)
  - LPW - General Correspondence - 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on LPW); Roswell B. Perkins, H. Alexander Smith
  - LPW - General Information - 1955-1956 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on LPW); James P. Mitchell
  - LPW - Committee Reports - 1955-1956 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    labor (benefits), veterans benefits, U. S. Senate (presidential appointments)
  - Labor Committee Bills - 1955-1956 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on LPW)
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Civil Rights - 1955 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    civil rights
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Special Subcommittee on S.1760 - 1955 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    labor (legislation); Buffalo Arms Inc.; Ralph F. Leo
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Education - 1955-1956 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    education; J. W. Fulbright
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Fair labor Standards Act - 1955-1956 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    labor (legislation); George Meany; Republican Party of Puerto Rico
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Subcommittee on Health - 1955-1956 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    health (legislation), public health; Ralph E. Flanders, James E. Murray
  - [U. S. Senate LPW] I.M.I. - Salk Vaccine - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate] Labor-Sub-committee - 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    labor (legislation), labor (working conditions)
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Minimum Wage Material - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    labor (wages); Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, CWA, Dept. of Labor
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - National Labor Relations Board - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    Philip Ray Ridgers
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Labor Nominations - 1955-1956 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    U. S. Senate (presidential appointment); Edward Martin
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Taft-Hartley Act - 1953, 1955 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Subcommittee on Unemployment in Certain Industries - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    labor (working conditions), unemployment; Paul H. Douglas
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Subcommittee on Veterans Affairs - 1955-1956 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    Veterans Affairs; CIO; H. Alexander Smith
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] S.Res 225 - Smith - Study and Investigation of employee welfare and pension funds" - 1953-1954 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    welfare and pension funds (investigation)
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] Employee Welfare and Pension Fund Investigation - LPW S.Res 270 - 1948-1954 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    welfare and pension funds, labor-management relations
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] LPW - File 1 - Welfare and Pension funds - 1955, 1957 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    labor (welfare and pension funds); Paul H. Douglas, Arthur J. Goldberg
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - File 2 - Welfare and Pension funds - 1956 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    labor (welfare and pension funds); Gordon Allott, Paul H. Douglas
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - File 3 - Pension and Welfare Subcommittee - 1956 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    labor (welfare and pension funds)
  - [U. S. Senate] LPW - Subcommittee on Pension and Welfare - 1954-1958 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    labor (Employee Benefits), welfare and pension plans; AFL-CIO, General Motors Corp.
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] Employee Welfare and Pension Fund Investigation - LPW Budget - 1954-1955 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    labor (employee benefits), welfare and pension funds; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] Employee Welfare and Pension Fund Investigation - LPW Correspondence - Subcommittee Investigation of Welfare funds - 1954 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    welfare and pension funds (investigation); Dr. Maurice I. Neufeld, Edward Martin, Everett Dirksen
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] Welfare and Pension Plans Investigation. Subcomm. On welfare and Pension funds - 84th Congress - 1956 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    U. S. Senate (Committee on LPW, Subcommittee on Welfare and Pension funds
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] Welfare and Pension - 84th Congress - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 18)
    welfare plans
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] I.M.I. - Hearing Outline - 7/10/55 - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 19)
    welfare and pension funds
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] I.M.I. - Hearing Outline, 11/29/55 - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 20)
    welfare funds, pension funds
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] I.M.I. - Hearing Outline, 11/28/55 - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 21)
    welfare, pension funds; United Mine Workers of America, United Auto Workers, AFL
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] I.M.I. - Hearing Outline, 11/30/55 - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 22)
    health insurance
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] I.M.I. - Hearing Outline, 12/1/55 - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 23)
    insurance funds
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] I.M.I. - Hearing Outline, 12/2/55 - 1955 (Box 201, Folder 24)
    health and welfare funds
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] Final Report of the Subcommittee on Welfare and Pension Funds - 84th Congress - 1955-1956 (Box 201, Folder 25)
    welfare, pension funds
  - [U. S. Senate. Committee on LPW] Welfare and Pension Subcommittee - 1957 (Box 201, Folder 26)
    welfare (legislation), pensions (legislation)
  - LPW - General Information - 1955, 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    education; AFL-CIO, Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare
  - [LPW] Legislative Recommendations of the President - 85th Congress - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    U. S. Congress (legislative proposals) - 85th Congress
  - LPW - Miscellaneous - 1955-1958 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    U. S. Senate (Comm. on LPW), education, labor; Marian [B. Folsom]; U. S. Dept. of Commerce, Small Business Administration
  - [LPW] List - Legislation to be Considered for Introduction - 1/57 - [1957] (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Labor Committee Bills - 1 - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    U. S. Senate (Comm. on LPW)
  - Labor Committee Bills - 2 - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Labor Committee Bills - 3 - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Labor Committee Bills - 4 - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Labor Committee Bills - 5 - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Education: - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    education (federal aid), education (higher); National Association and Council of Business Schools; Joseph R. Strokel
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Education - 1947, 1956-1957 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    education (federal aid), education (higher); President's Committee of Scientists and Engineers, U. S. Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Education 2 - 1958 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    education (higher), education (federal aid), education (vocational); U. S. Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare; Elliot L. Richardson
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Education - 1958 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    education (federal aid); U. S. Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare
  - LPW - School Construction - 1957 (Box 202, Folder 14)
    educational facilities, school construction; Stules Bridges
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Civil Rights - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 15)
    civil rights (legislation); American Civil Liberties Union, U. A. W., American Jewish Committee
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Health - 1957-1958 (Box 202, Folder 16)
    health (rehabilitation), health (cancer research); General Foods Corp., National Health Education Comm.
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Health - 1957 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    education (health), nursing, health (services)
  - [LPW] I.M.I. - F. L. S. A. - 85th - 1957 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    labor (legislation), Fair Labor Standards Act
  - LPW - Fair Labor Standards Act - 1957-1958 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    labor (legislation) Fair Labor Standards Act; Chamber of Commerce of the U. S., AFL-CIO, National Consumers League
  - [LPW] S.1267 - To amend Fair Labor Standards Act of 1938 - 1957 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    Fair Labor Standards Act, employment (discrimination)
  - [LPW] Fair Labor Standards Act - as amended - 1957 - 85th - 1957 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act - 85th Congress - misc. material - 1957 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Labor - 1957-1958 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    labor (legislation); UAW; James Mitchell, Paul H. Douglas
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Labor - 1958 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    labor (legislation); AFL-CIO; Barry Goldwater
  - LPW - Labor Comm. - 1956-1957 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    labor; International Labor Office
  - LPW - Legislation, Subcommittee Report - 1957 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    labor (legislation), labor (congressional investigation)
  - [LPW] Misc. Labor Legislation - 85th Congress - 1958 (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - LPW: Minimum Wage Material - 1957 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    labor (wages), minimum wage
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Railroad Retirement - 1957-1958 (Box 203, Folder 13)
    employee benefits
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Veterans Affairs - 1957-1958 (Box 203, Folder 14)
  - LPW - Subcommittee on Welfare and Pension regulation. 85th Congress - 1956-1957 (Box 203, Folder 15)
    public welfare (legislation) pension funds
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] S. Res. 74, S.3974 - 85th Congress Labor (investigation) - 1957-1958 (Box 203, Folder 16)
    labor (investigation)
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Select Labor Committee - General Information - 1 - 1957-1958 (Box 203, Folder 17)
    labor (investigation); Barry Goldwater; U. A. W.
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Select Labor Committee - General Information - 2a - 1957-1958 (Box 203, Folder 18)
    labor (investigation); James P. Mitchell
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Select Labor Committee - General Information - 2b - 1957-1958 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Select Labor Committee - General Information - 3 - 1957-1958 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    labor (investigation); John McClellan, Walter P. Reuther
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Misc. - Select Comm. File - 1957 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    labor (investigation); Karl Mundt, Robert F. Kennedy
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Select Labor Committee - Committee Business - 1957-1958 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    labor (investigation), U. S. Senate (Select Committee on Improper Activities in the Labor/Management Field); Robert F. Kennedy (memos - no signatures)
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Employment - 1957 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    labor (investigation of), U. S. Senate (Select Committee on Improper Activities in the Labor/Management. Field); Jean T. McKelvey, Barry Goldwater
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Select Labor Committee: material forwarded to Staff and Employment - 1957-1958 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    labor (investigation), U. S. Senate (Select Labor Comm.); Howard W. Robison
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Scranton, Pennsylvania Hearings - 1957, 19-- (Box 204, Folder 7)
    labor (congressional investigation)
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Teamster hearings. Portland, Oregon, 1957 - 1957 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Bobby Baker - 1958 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] I.M.I. - 1957 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    labor unions (investigation of)
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Untitled - 1957 (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Select Labor Committee - Walter P. Reuther Statement - 1958 (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - Testimony Before Senate Labor Subcommittee of Senate Committee on LPW - 1958 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    labor (legislation); Wm. Knowland, John McClellan, H. Alexander Smith, George Meany
  - [U.S. Senate. LPW] Misc. papers - LPW - Subcommittee on Labor - 85th Congress - Hearings re Improper Labor activities - 1949-1950, 1957-1958 (Box 204, Folder 14)
    labor (Congress investigation)
  - [U.S. Senate] LPW - 85th Congress - McClellan Comm. - Select Committee on Improper Labor? - 1957-1958 (Box 204, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Booklets - Proposed Amendments to NLRA - vol. 8 & 9 - 1939-1940 (Box 204, Folder 16)
    labor (legislation), U. S. House of Representatives, Committee on Labor
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Labor Pamphlets - Misc. - Prior to 1947 - 1946-1947 (Box 204, Folder 17)
    labor; Homer Ferguson "Why Not Labor Courts ," NRLA - War Labor Disputes Act, Guide to NRLA, Report on Wage Policy - S. H. Slichter, N. A. M. Law Digest, Machinery and Allied Products, Factory Management?
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Suggestions - Revisions in Labor Laws - Prior to (80th, 1st) - 1947 (Box 204, Folder 18)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] I.M.I. Bill: S871, S.872, SJRes 85 - 1947 (Box 204, Folder 19)
    labor relations (legislation)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] S.1126 - 1947 (Box 204, Folder 20)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] S.1126 NLRA of 1947 - 1947 (Box 204, Folder 21)
    labor management relations
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] S.1126 - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Conference on Comm. Prints: H. R. 3020 - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Congressional Voting - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Senate Record - March 10 - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] H. R. 3020 - 1941, 1947 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    labor (legislation), Taft Hartley
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Suggested Amendment to H. R. 3020 - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    labor (legislation); Philip Murray, Ralph [W. Gwinn], Richard H. Pass
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] H. R. 3020 - Explanation - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    labor (legislation); Fred J. Hartley; governmental affairs - legislation daily
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Ball's program - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    labor (legislation); CIO
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Committee Hearings - 1 - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    labor (legislation); U. S. Congress. Committee on LPW
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Conference Committee - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    labor (legislation); Charles E. Wilson
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] (80th, 1st) Legislation Introduced - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    labor (legislation); Survey Graphic
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Mr. Shugrue - Labor Bills - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Veto Message - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    labor (legislation); Harry S. Truman
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Material Re: Taft-Hartley Law FEPC and Anti-Discrimination Bill; other speeches and material in Labor-Management Relations C 1947 - 1946-1947 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    labor-management relations; Arthur V. Watkins
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] P L 101 Press - 1947-1948 (Box 205, Folder 17)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] P L 101 - Press - 1947-1948 (Box 205, Folder 18)
    labor (legislation), Taft-Hartley (Ph. 101); General Electric, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Laws re Unionization - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Industry-wide Bargaining - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 20)
    labor (industry-wide bargaining)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] P L 101 - Suggestions for Change - 1948 (Box 205, Folder 21)
    labor (legislation), Taft-Hartley; Richard H. Pass
  - Joint Congressional Committee Bills to Amend P L 101 - 1948 (Box 205, Folder 22)
    labor (legislation), Taft-Hartley (proposed amendments)
  - [Taft-Hartley] Joint Congressional Comm. Hearings - 5/24 - 1948 (Box 205, Folder 23)
    labor (legislation), labor-management relations; Robert Akelow, Paul M. Herzog; U. S. CJCLMR
  - [U. S. Senate. - Taft-Hartley] Proposed Senate and House Bills - 80th Congress - 1st Session re LPW - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 25)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] I.M.I. Preliminary Program - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 26)
    labor (legislation), I & L R
  - [LPW - Taft-Hartley] Senate Comm. - March - Omnibus Bill by DWS - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 27)
    labor (legislation); Dwyer W. Shugrue
  - [LPW - Taft-Hartley] Senate Con. 4/7 - Tentative Print - 1947 (Box 205, Folder 28)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] S. 1126 - Amendments - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] S. 1126 - Analysis of draft - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    labor (legislation); Paul M. Herzog
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Taft-Hartley Act - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    labor (legislation - Taft-Hartley Act)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] H. R. 3020 - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Amendment to S.1126 N. Y. S. Board of Mediation - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] S.1126 Explanation - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] P L 101 - Opinion Research Corp. Survey - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Reilly-Analysis of P L 101 - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    labor (legislation - Taft-Hartley Act); Gerard D. Reilly, Raymond S. Smethurst
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Publications Subsequent to P L 101 The Typographical Journal - 1947-1948 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] P L 101 Explanations - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Taft-Hartley - Press analysis - 1947-1949 (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Apprentice Training - 1948 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    labor (apprentice training)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Inland Steel Information - 1948 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    labor (legislation - Taft Hartley Act); Inland Steel Company
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Data on Wages and Profits - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 14)
    labor (legislation - Taft Hartley Act)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Industries - Description - 1947-1948 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    labor (union activity), rope (Industry); Columbian Rope Co., Carl Ahlers, Inc.
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Judicial Decisions - 1947 (Box 206, Folder 16)
    labor (legislation), union shop, labor (judicial decisions)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Investigation of the Causes of Labor Disputes - hearings? - 1946 (Box 206, Folder 17)
    U. S. House of Representatives (common labor)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] H. R. 82st Congress 1st session - NLRA of 1949 - 1949 (Box 206, Folder 18)
    labor (legislation); U. S. Congress - House of Representatives
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Labor legislation - misc. material - 1949 (Box 206, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Labor Relations - Data pertaining to Labor Relations Legislation - Misc. - I - 1948-1949 (Box 206, Folder 20)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW - Taft-Hartley] Labor Relations - Data pertaining to Labor Relations Legislation - Misc. - II - 1949 (Box 206, Folder 21)
    labor (legislation), NLRA of 1949, Israel